THE DATE
約會
They called from work, I have to go.
公司打來了，我真的要走了。
You need to take care of that date now.
現在你要負責處理那個約會了。
Do I have to?
一定要嘛...?
Yes you do. It's not a big deal,
對，你一定要。
you know the drill.
這沒什麼啦，你知道流程的
It' Lissu from Oh Lala and that Mirka with Nefertiti,
從 Oh Lala來的 Lissu和那個 Mirka 帶著娜芙蒂蒂,
I think you have met them.
我想你已經見過他們了。
Fine.
好啦。
Thanks honey. It'll be just fine.
謝啦親愛的。一定沒問題的。
Call me if there's something.
如果有事情就打給我唷。
Yeah, just go.
好啦，你走吧。
Hi!
嗨！
Welcome.
歡迎
Well hello Tino!
哇！Tino 哈囉！
It's been a while since I saw you.
距離上次看到你已經好久了唷！
You're a grown man now.
你現在是個男人了。
There's some coat hangers there I think.
我想那邊有一些外套的掛勾。
Hi.
嗨。
Let's leave them to get to know each other.
我們給它們一些私人空間認識一下彼此吧
Nefertiti has been screaming for three nights.
娜芙蒂蒂已經叫了足足三個晚上了。
I'm really stressed about this all.
我這樣真的壓力很大耶
You always stress so much.
你對什麼事都感到壓力很大阿
The nature takes it course.
大自然有它的時間表。
I just got a letter.
我剛剛收到一封信。
Maserati,
瑪莎拉蒂，
Nefertiti's half sister from the father's side -
娜芙蒂蒂同父異母的姐姐----
is a Quadruple Grand Champion.
是隻超級冠軍貓！
Can you imagine, that little frog?
你能想像嘛？那隻醜喵喵？
Nice. She is pretty.
不錯阿，她很漂亮。
How did Diablo do this season?
暗黑破壞神這季表現如何？
He got some rosettes.
他有拿到一些彩帶。
Nefertiti is only flirting.
娜芙蒂蒂只是在調情。
Some flirting.
調情調成這樣
She is screaming "Fuck me!"
她在尖叫[快上我！]
"Now! Now! Right now!"
[現在！現在！就是現在！]
That sounds just like it is suppose to sound.
[這種聲音很正常啦！]
Good boy!
好傢伙！
That was fast.
動作還滿快的嘛！
What is that fat ass stud doing to her?
那個混蛋在對她做什麼？！
Timing was just right, she was very willing.
時機很好，她看起來很樂意
Let's give Diablo a chance
我們給暗黑破壞神一些時間讓
to do his thing a couple of times.
他有機會多忙幾次
That sounds just terrible.
那些聲音真的太淒慘了
I'm sorry I got so upset.
對不起我反應這麼大
It's just that Neffi is so little
只是蒂蒂還這麼小，
and it's her first time.
而且這又是她的第一次...
Diablo is a good stud.
暗黑破壞神是隻好種貓，
He has never hurt any queens.
他從來不會傷到任何公主
Are you sure?
你確定嘛？
Yeah. He's really experienced and patient.
嗯，他很有經驗而且很有耐心。
She'll be ok.
她會沒事的。
I'm sure you right.
我相信你是對的。
Yeah.
嗯。
Thanks for the coffee and - for the stud.
謝謝你的咖啡---還有貓種。
That's ok.
不用客氣。
Thanks, Tino.
謝了，Tino。